<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<songDB>
<type>XMLsong</type>
<disclaimer>The copyrights to these songs belongs to person mentioned in the copyright tag of each song. This database has been designed and compiled for VerseVIEW only.</disclaimer>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>Above all Power</name>
  <font>Noto Sans Kannada SemiBold</font>
  <font2></font2>
  <timestamp>5/3/2025  17:57</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd></bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[Above all powers, above all kings Above all nature and all created things<BR>Above all wisdom and all the ways of man You were here before the world began<BR><slide>Above all kingdoms, above all thrones Above all wonders the world has ever known<BR>Above all wealth and treasures of the earth There's no way to measure what You're worth<slide>Crucified, and laid behind a stone You lived to die, rejected and alone<BR>Like a rose trampled on the ground You took the fall and thought of me<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>Alas And Did My Savior Bleed</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2></font2>
  <timestamp>5/28/2020  17:34</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd>null</bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[Alas, and did my Savior bleed<BR>And did my Sovereign die?<slide>Would He devote that sacred head,<BR>For such a worm as I. <slide>Was it for crimes that I have done,<BR>He suffered on the tree?<slide>Amazing pity, grace unknown,<BR>And love beyond degree! <slide>Well might the sun in darkness hide<BR>And shut His glories in;<slide>When Christ the mighty Maker died<BR>For man, the creature's sin. <slide>Thus might I hide my blushing face<BR>While His dear cross appears;<slide>Dissolve my heart in thankfulness<BR>And melt mine eyes to tears. <slide>But drops of grief can ne'er repay,<BR>The debt of love I owe;<slide>Here, Lord, I give myself away,<BR>'Tis all that I can do.<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide><slide><slide><slide><slide><slide><slide><slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[null]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[null]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[null]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>All to Jesus I surrender</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2></font2>
  <timestamp>11/29/2025  8:59</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd></bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[All to Jesus I surrender,<BR>All to Him I freely give;<BR>I will ever love and trust Him,<BR>In His presence daily live. <slide>I surrender all,<BR>I surrender all.<BR>All to Thee my blessed Savior,<BR>I surrender all. <slide>All to Jesus I surrender,<BR>Humbly at His feet I bow,<BR>Worldly pleasures all forsaken,<BR>Take me Jesus take me now. <slide>All to Jesus I surrender,<BR>Make me Savior wholly Thine;<BR>Let me feel the Holy Spirit,<BR>Truly know that Thou art mine. <slide>All to Jesus I surrender,<BR>Lord I give myself to Thee.<BR>Fill me with Thy love and power;<BR>Let Thy blessings fall on me. <slide>All to Jesus I surrender,<BR>Now I feel the sacred flame.<BR>Oh the joy of full salvation!<BR>Glory, glory to His name<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide><slide><slide><slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[I Surrender All]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[null]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>All to Jesus I surrender</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2></font2>
  <timestamp>11/29/2025  9:15</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd></bkgnd>
  <key>D</key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[All to Jesus I surrender, All to Him I freely give<BR>I will ever love and trust Him, In His presence daily live<slide>I surrender all, I surrender all<BR>All to Thee my blessed Savior, I surrender all<slide>All to Jesus I surrender, Lord I give myself to Thee<BR>Fill me with Your love and power, Let Your blessings fall on me<slide>All to Jesus I surrender, Now I feel the sacred flame<BR>Oh the joy of full salvation! Glory, glory to Your name<slide>All to Jesus I surrender,<BR>Humbly at His feet I bow,<BR>Worldly pleasures all forsaken,<BR>Take me Jesus take me now. <slide>All to Jesus I surrender,<BR>Make me Savior wholly Thine;<BR>Let me feel the Holy Spirit,<BR>Truly know that Thou art mine. <slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide><slide><slide><slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[I Surrender All]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[null]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>Angels We Have Heard On High</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2>null</font2>
  <timestamp>null</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd></bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[Gloria, in excelsis Deo!<BR>Gloria, in excelsis Deo! <slide>Angels we have heard on high,<BR>Sweetly singing o'er the plains;<BR>And the mountains in reply,<BR>Echoing their joyous strains. <slide>Shepherds, why this jubilee?<BR>Why your joyous strains prolong?<BR>Say what may the tidings be;<BR>Which inspire your heav'nly song? <slide>Come to Bethlehem and see,<BR>Him whose birth the angels sing;<BR>Come adore on bended knee,<BR>Christ the Lord, the newborn King. <slide>See within a manger laid,<BR>Jesus, Lord of heav'n and earth;<BR>Mary, Joseph, lend your aid,<BR>With us sing our Savior's birth.<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[null]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[null]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[null]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>Away In A Manger</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2></font2>
  <timestamp>5/28/2020  16:1</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd>null</bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[Away in a manger no crib for a bed;<BR>The little Lord Jesus lay down His sweet head.<slide>The stars in the sky looked down where He lay;<BR>The little Lord Jesus asleep on the hay. <slide>The cattle are lowing the baby awakes;<BR>But little Lord Jesus no crying He makes.<slide>I love Thee, Lord Jesus, look down from the sky;<BR>And stay by my cradle till morning is nigh. <slide>Be near me, Lord Jesus, I ask Thee to stay;<BR>Close by me forever and love me I pray.<slide>Bless all the dear children in Thy tender care;<BR>And take us to heaven to live with Thee there.<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide><slide><slide><slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[null]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[null]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[null]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>Awesome God</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2>null</font2>
  <timestamp>null</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd></bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[Our God is an awesome God<BR>He reigns from heaven above<BR>With wisdom pow'r and love<BR>Our God is an awesome God<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[null]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[null]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[null]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>Behold the King has come Divinity</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2></font2>
  <timestamp>12/18/2022  8:52</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd>null</bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[Behold, the King has come Divinity incarnate<BR>Creator of the world Breathing our air<slide>Behold what light has come And the dark cannot contain it The Savior of the world<BR>Is finally here<slide>Oh, come, let us adore Him Come, let us adore Him For He alone is worthy Christ the Lord<slide>Behold, the Father's love Beyond all comprehension He gave His only Son<BR>To die in our place<slide>Go and see that empty tomb He’s not there, for He is risen Every heart prеpare Him room<BR>Jesus Christ, the King of Hеaven<slide>We give You all the glory We give You all the glory We give you all the glory Christ the Lord<slide>We praise Your name<BR>(We praise Your name forever)<BR>Jesus we praise Your name forever<BR>Christ the Lord<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide><slide><slide><slide><slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[null]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[undefined]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>Bless the Lord oh my soul</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2></font2>
  <timestamp>11/9/2024  21:1</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd></bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[Bless the Lord oh my soul Oh my soul worship His Holy Name <BR>Sing like never before Oh my soul I’ll worship Your Holy Name<slide>The sun comes up it’s a new day dawning<BR>It’s time to sing Your song again Whatever may pass and whatever lies before me <BR>Let me be singing when the evening comes<slide>You’re rich in love and You’re slow to anger Your name is great And Your heart is kind For all Your goodness I will keep on singing <BR>Ten thousand reasons for my heart to find<slide>And on that day when my strength is failing The end draws near and my time has come Still my soul will sing Your praise unending <BR>Ten thousand years and forevermore<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide><slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>Blessed Be The Name</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2>null</font2>
  <timestamp>null</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd></bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[Blessed be the name,<BR>Blessed be the name,<BR>Blessed be the name of the Lord;<BR>Blessed be the name,<BR>Blessed be the name,<BR>Blessed be the name of the Lord. <slide>All praise to Him who reigns above,<BR>In majesty supreme<BR>Who gave His Son for man to die,<BR>That He might man redeem! <slide>His name above all names shall stand,<BR>Exalted more and more,<BR>At God the Father's own right hand,<BR>Where angel hosts adore. <slide>Redeemer, Savior, Friend of man,<BR>Once ruined by the fall,<BR>Thou hast devised salvation's plan,<BR>For Thou hast died for all. <slide>His name shall be the Counselor,<BR>The mighty Prince of Peace,<BR>Of all earth's kingdoms Conqueror,<BR>Whose reign shall never cease.<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[null]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[null]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[null]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>Blessed Be The Name Of The Lord</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2></font2>
  <timestamp>12/7/2024  21:41</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd></bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[Blessed be the Name of the Lord <BR>Blessed be the Name of the Lord <BR>Blessed be the Name of the Lord Most High<slide>The Name of the Lord is as strong as tower<BR>The righteous run into it and they are saved<slide>Glory to the Name of the Lord Glory to the Name of the Lord Glory to the Name of the Lord Most High<slide>Holy is the Name of the Lord <BR>Holy is the Name of the Lord <BR>Holy is the Name of the Lord Most High<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide><slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>Blessed be your name in the land</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2></font2>
  <timestamp>11/19/2022  15:31</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd>null</bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[Blessed be Your name In the land that is plentiful Where Your streams of abundance flow Blessed be Your name<slide>Blessed be Your name When I'm found in the desert place Though I walk through the wilderness Blessed be Your name<slide>Every blessing You pour out I'll turn back to praise When the darkness closes in, Lord<BR>Still I will say<slide>Blessed be the name of the Lord Blessed be Your name Blessed be the name of the Lord<BR>Blessed be Your glorious name<slide>Blessed be Your name When the sun's shining down on me When the world's all as it should be<BR>Blessed be Your name<slide>Blessed be Your name On the road marked with suffering Though there's pain in the offering<BR>Blessed be Your name<slide>You give and take away You give and take away<BR>My heart will choose to say Lord, blessed be Your name<BR><slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide><slide><slide><slide><slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[undefined]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>Carols Verses</name>
  <font>Arial</font>
  <font2></font2>
  <timestamp>12/18/2022  8:38</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd>null</bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[For unto us a Child is born, Unto us a Son is given; And the government will be upon His shoulder. And His name will be called Wonderful, Counselor, Mighty God, Everlasting Father, Prince of Peace.<BR>Isaiah 9:6<slide>But when the fullness of the time had come, God sent forth His Son, born of a woman, born under the law, to redeem those who were under the law, that we might receive the adoption as sons.<BR>Galatians 4:4‭-‬5<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[undefined]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>Cast your burden on the lord do not be troubled</name>
  <font>Arial</font>
  <font2>Arial</font2>
  <timestamp>11/12/2022  8:45</timestamp>
  <yvideo>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cLfwXzN4pdI</yvideo>
  <bkgnd>null</bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[Cast your burden on the lord do not be troubled.<BR> And he shall sustain you he will make a way for you<slide>He'll never permit the righteous to be moved. He will guide him day by day.<slide>The lord's your keeper he's your shade he will be in all your ways.<slide>If god is for us why to worry who be against us no worry.<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide><slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[SUNDAYSCHOOL]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[undefined]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>Count Your Blessings</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2></font2>
  <timestamp>12/28/2024  21:0</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd></bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[When upon life's billows You are tempest tossed,<BR>When you are discouraged Thinking all is lost,<BR>Count your many blessings Name them one by one,<BR>And it will surprise you What the Lord hath done. <slide>Count your blessings Name them one by one.<BR>Count your blessings See what God hath done.<BR>Count your blessings Name them one by one.<BR>Count your many blessings See what God hath done. <slide>Are you ever burdened With a load of care,<BR>Does the cross seem heavy You are called to bear.<BR>Count your many blessings Every doubt will fly,<BR>And you will be singing As the days go by. <slide>So amid the conflict Whether great or small,<BR>Do not be discouraged God is over all.<BR>Count your many blessings Angels will attend,<BR>Help and comfort give you To your journey's end.<slide>When you look at others With their lands and gold,<BR>Think that Christ has promised You His wealth untold.<BR>Count your many blessings Money cannot buy,<BR>Your reward in heaven Nor your home on high. <slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide><slide><slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[null]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>Create In Me A Clean Heart</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2>null</font2>
  <timestamp>null</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd></bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[Create in me a clean heart<BR>O Lord my God<BR>And renew a right spirit within me<BR>Create in me a clean heart<BR>O Lord my God<BR>And renew a right spirit within me<slide>Cast me not away from Thy presence O Lord<BR>Take not Thy Holy Spirit from me<BR>Restore to me the joy of Thy salvation<BR>And renew a right spirit within me<slide>Lord renew my spirit and restore my soul<slide>Create in me a clean heart<BR>O Lord my God<BR>And renew a right spirit within me<BR>Within me<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[null]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[null]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[null]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>Everyone Needs Compassion</name>
  <font>Arial</font>
  <font2>Arial</font2>
  <timestamp>8/19/2023  16:57</timestamp>
  <yvideo>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cLfwXzN4pdI</yvideo>
  <bkgnd>null</bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[Everyone Needs Compassion, Love That’s Never Failing<BR>Let Mercy Fall On Me.<BR>Everyone Needs Forgiveness, The Kindness Of The Saviour<BR>The Hope Of Nations.<slide>Saviour, He Can Move The Mountains, My God Is Mighty To Save<BR>He's Mighty To Save. Forever, Author Of Salvation<BR>He Rose And Conquered The Grave. Jesus Conquered The Grave.<slide>So Take Me As You Find Me, All My Fears And Failures,<BR> Fill My Life Again.<BR> I Give My Life To Follow Everything I Believe In, Now I Surrender<slide>Shine your light and let the whole world see.<BR> We're singing for the glory of the risen king Jesus<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide><slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[SUNDAYSCHOOL]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[undefined]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>Give thanks with a grateful heart</name>
  <font>Arial</font>
  <font2>Arial</font2>
  <timestamp>4/23/2022  8:14</timestamp>
  <yvideo>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cLfwXzN4pdI</yvideo>
  <bkgnd>null</bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[Give thanks with a grateful heart Give thanks to the Holy One Give thanks because He’s given Jesus Christ, His Son<slide>And now let the weak say, “I am strong”<BR>Let the poor say, “I am rich Because of what the Lord has done for us”<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[SUNDAYSCHOOL]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[undefined]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>Glory To His Name</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2>null</font2>
  <timestamp>null</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd></bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[Glory to His name,<BR>Glory to His name,<BR>All may change,<BR>But Jesus never,<BR>Glory to His name.<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[null]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[null]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[null]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>God is fighting for us</name>
  <font>Times New Roman</font>
  <font2></font2>
  <timestamp>6/12/2022  8:50</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd>null</bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[God is fighting for us, God is on our side He has overcome, Yes He has overcome<BR>We will not be shaken, We will not be moved Jesus You are here<BR><BR><slide>Carrying our burdens, Covering our shame He has overcome, Yes He has overcome We will not be shaken, We will not be moved Jesus You are here<slide>I will live, I will not die The resurrection power of Christ Alive in me and I am free In Jesus' Name<BR><slide>I will live, I will not die I will declare and lift You high, Christ revealed and I am healed In Jesus' Name<slide>God is fighting for us, Pushing back the darkness Lighting up the Kingdom That cannot be shaken In the Name of Jesus, Enemy's defeated And we will shout it out, Shout it out<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide><slide><slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[null]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[undefined]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>God is good all the time He put a song of praise</name>
  <font>Aruna</font>
  <font2>Alegreya Sans</font2>
  <timestamp>10/5/2024  20:46</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd></bkgnd>
  <key>D</key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[God is good all the time He put a song of praise in this heart of mine God is good all the time Through the darkest night, His light will shine God is good, God is good all the time<slide>If you're walking through the valley And there are shadows all around Do not fear, He will guide you<BR>He will keep you safe and sound He has promised to never leave you Nor forsake you, and His word is true<slide>We were sinners and so unworthy Still for us He chose to die Filled us with His Holy Spirit<BR>Now we can stand and testify That His love is everlasting And His mercies, they will never end<slide>Though I may not understand All the plans you have for me My life is in your hands And through the eyes of faith I can clearly see<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide><slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>God will make a way Where there seems to be no way</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2>Alegreya Sans</font2>
  <timestamp>9/7/2024  19:9</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd></bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[God will make a way Where there seems to be no way <BR>He works in ways we cannot see He will make a way for me<slide>He will be my guide Hold me closely to His side <BR>With love and strength for each new day<BR>He will make a way, He will make a way<slide>By a roadway in the wilderness, He'll lead me<BR>And rivers in the desert will I see <BR>Heaven and Earth will fade but His Word will still remain<BR>And He will do something new today<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>Hallelujah Hallelujah Hallelujah Hallelujah</name>
  <font>Times New Roman</font>
  <font2></font2>
  <timestamp>1/22/2023  8:46</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd>null</bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[Hallelujah, Hallelujah Hallelujah, Hallelujah<BR>Hallelujah, Hallelujah Hallelujah, Hallelujah<slide>Thankyou father Thankyou father<BR>Thankyou father Thankyou father<slide>Thankyou Jesus Thankyou Jesus<BR>Thankyou Jesus Thankyou Jesus<slide>Thankyou HolySpirit Thankyou HolySpirit<BR>Thankyou HolySpirit Thankyou HolySpirit<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide><slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[undefined]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>Hallelujah, Hallelujah, for our Lord God</name>
  <font>Times New Roman</font>
  <font2></font2>
  <timestamp>10/1/2022  19:59</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd>null</bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[Hallelujah, Hallelujah, for our Lord God Almighty Reig Hallelujah, Hallelujah, for our Lord God Almighty Reign Hallelujah<slide>Holy, Holy Are you Lord God Almighty<BR>Worthy is the Lamb Worthy is the Lamb<BR>You are Holy, Holy<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[null]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[undefined]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>Hark The Herald Angels Sing</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2>null</font2>
  <timestamp>null</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd></bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[Hark! the herald angels sing,<BR>"Glory to the newborn King;<BR>Peace on earth and mercy mild,<BR>God and sinners reconciled."<BR>Joyful, all ye nations, rise,<BR>Join the triumph of the skies;<BR>With angelic hosts proclaim,<BR>"Christ is born in Bethlehem."<BR>Hark! the herald angels sing,<BR>"Glory to the newborn King." <slide>Christ, by highest heav'n adored,<BR>Christ, the everlasting Lord;<BR>Late in time behold Him come,<BR>Offspring of a virgin's womb.<BR>Veiled in flesh the Godhead see,<BR>Hail, the incarnate Deity!<BR>Pleased as man with men to dwell,<BR>Jesus our Emmanuel.<BR>Hark! the herald angels sing,<BR>"Glory to the newborn King." <slide>Hail the heav'n born Prince of Peace!<BR>Hail the Sun of righteousness!<BR>Light and life to all He brings,<BR>Ris'n with healing in His wings.<BR>Mild He lays His glory by,<BR>Born that man no more may die;<BR>Born to raise the sons of earth,<BR>Born to give them second birth.<BR>Hark! the herald angels sing,<BR>"Glory to the newborn King!" <slide>Come, Desire of nations, come!<BR>Fix in us Thy humble home.<BR>Rise, the woman's conqu'ring seed,<BR>Bruise in us the serpent's head;<BR>Adam's likeness now efface,<BR>Stamp Thine image in its place;<BR>Second Adam from above,<BR>Reinstate us in Thy love.<BR>Hark! the herald angels sing,<BR>"Glory to the newborn King."<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[null]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[null]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[null]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>Hear our prayer We are Your children</name>
  <font>Noto Sans Kannada SemiBold</font>
  <font2></font2>
  <timestamp>5/3/2025  21:7</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd></bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[Hear our prayer We are Your children<BR>And we've gathered here today, We're gathered here to pray<slide>Hear our cry Lord, we need Your mercy<BR>And we need Your grace today, Hear us as we pray<slide>Our Father, who art in Heaven Hallowed be thy name Our Father, hear us from Heaven<BR>Forgive our sins we pray<slide>Hear our song As it rises to Heaven<BR>May Your glory fill the earth As the waters cover the seas<slide>See our hearts And remove anything That is standing in the way Of coming to You today<slide>And though we are few We're surrounded by many Who have crossed that river before<BR>And this is the song we'll be singing forever<BR>Holy is the Lord Holy is the Lord Holy is the Lord Holy is the Lord<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide><slide><slide><slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>Holy Spirit Thou Art Welcome</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2>null</font2>
  <timestamp>null</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd></bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[Holy Spirit Thou art welcome in this place<BR>Holy Spirit Thou art welcome in this place<BR>Omnipotent Father of mercy and grace<BR>Thou art welcome in this place<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[null]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[null]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[null]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>I Am Thine O Lord</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2>null</font2>
  <timestamp>null</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd></bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[Draw me nearer, nearer blessed Lord,<BR>To the cross where Thou hast died.<BR>Draw me nearer, nearer, nearer blessed Lord.<BR>To Thy precious bleeding side. <slide>I am Thine O Lord; I have heard Thy voice,<BR>And it told Thy love to me.<BR>But I long to rise in the arms of faith,<BR>And be closer drawn to Thee. <slide>Consecrate me now to Thy service Lord,<BR>By the power of grace divine.<BR>Let my soul look up with a steadfast hope,<BR>And my will be lost in Thine. <slide>Oh the pure delight of a single hour<BR>That before Thy throne I spend,<BR>When I kneel in prayer and with Thee my God,<BR>I commune as friend with friend! <slide>There are depths of love that I cannot know<BR>Till I cross the narrow sea;<BR>There are heights of joy that I may not reach<BR>Till I rest in peace with Thee.<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[null]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[null]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[null]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>I come before You today And there's just one thing that I want to say</name>
  <font>Times New Roman</font>
  <font2></font2>
  <timestamp>11/27/2022  8:47</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd>null</bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[I come before You today And there's just one thing that I want to say Thank You Lord Thank You Lord For all You've given to me<BR>For all the blessings that I can not see Thank You Lord Thank You Lord<slide>With a grateful heart With a song of praise<BR>With an outstretched arm I will bless Your name Thank You Lord I just wanna thank You Lord Thank You Lord I just wanna thank You Lord Thank You Lord<slide>For all You've done in my life You took my darkness and gave me your light Thank You Lord Thank You Lord You took my sin and my shame You took my sickness and healed all my pain Thank You Lord Thank You Lord<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[null]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[undefined]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>I will sing sing a new song to Jesus</name>
  <font>Arial</font>
  <font2>Arial</font2>
  <timestamp>12/16/2023  22:24</timestamp>
  <yvideo>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1fTK-zUmDuo</yvideo>
  <bkgnd>null</bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[I will sing, sing a new song to Jesus<BR>Celebrate His name I will sing, sing and glorify And <BR>Celebrate the King<BR><slide>He washed me by his blood He healed me by his stripes He comforted me through his words (2) <BR>He strengthened me by his Spirit (2)<BR><slide>I will cling to Thee I will trust in Thee<BR>You fill my heart with peace (2) <BR>You bless me all my life (2)<BR><slide>Wonderful are you Lord Counselor are you Lord <BR>Almighty God forever (2)<BR>King and Lord of Lords (2)<BR><slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide><slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[undefined]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>In The Sweet By And By</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2>null</font2>
  <timestamp>null</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd></bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[In the sweet by and by,<BR>In the sweet by and by,<BR>I'll have a mansion so bright and fair,<BR>Won't it be glorious when I get there,<BR>In the sweet by and by,<BR>In the sweet by and by,<BR>When the battle is done,<BR>And the vict'ry is won,<BR>In the sweet by and by. <slide>In the sweet by and by,<BR>In the sweet by and by,<BR>I'll stand at last on the street of pure gold,<BR>Wonders and glory of heav'n behold,<BR>In the sweet by and by,<BR>In the sweet by and by,<BR>Joy will be so complete when my Savior I meet,<BR>In the sweet by and by.<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[null]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[null]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[null]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>Jesus Loves The Little Children</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2>null</font2>
  <timestamp>null</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd></bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[Jesus loves the little children,<BR>All the children of the world.<BR>Red and yellow, black and white,<BR>They are precious in His sight--<BR>Jesus loves the little children of the world. <slide>Jesus died for all the children,<BR>All the children of the world.<BR>Red and yellow, black and white,<BR>All are precious in His sight--<BR>Jesus died for all the children of the world.<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[null]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[null]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[null]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>Joy To The World</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2>null</font2>
  <timestamp>null</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd></bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[Joy to the world! the Lord is come;<BR>Let earth receive her King.<BR>Let every heart prepare Him room,<BR>And heav'n and nature sing,<BR>And heav'n and nature sing,<BR>And heav'n and heav'n and nature sing. <slide>Joy to the earth! the Savior reigns;<BR>Let men their songs employ.<BR>While fields and floods,<BR>Rocks, hills and plains,<BR>Repeat the sounding joy,<BR>Repeat the sounding joy,<BR>Repeat, repeat the sounding joy. <slide>No more let sins and sorrows grow,<BR>Nor thorns infest the ground.<BR>He comes to make His blessings flow,<BR>Far as the curse is found,<BR>Far as the curse is found,<BR>Far as, far as the curse is found. <slide>He rules the world with truth and grace<BR>And makes the nations prove.<BR>The glories of His righteousness<BR>And wonders of His love,<BR>And wonders of His love,<BR>And wonders, and wonders of His love.<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[null]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[null]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[null]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>Light of the world You stepped down into darkness</name>
  <font>Noto Sans Kannada SemiBold</font>
  <font2>Alegreya Sans</font2>
  <timestamp>5/17/2025  19:21</timestamp>
  <yvideo>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cLfwXzN4pdI</yvideo>
  <bkgnd></bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[Light of the world You stepped down into darkness<BR>Opened my eyes, Let me see<BR>Beauty that made this heart adore you<BR>Hope of a life spent with you<slide>Here I am to worship Here I am to bow down<BR>Here I am to say that you're my God<BR>You're altogether lovely Altogether worthy<BR>Altogether wonderful to me<slide>King of all days So highly exalted<BR>Glorious in heaven above<BR>Humbly you came to the earth you created<BR>All for love's sake became poor<slide>I'll never know how much it cost <BR>To see my sin upon that cross<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide><slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>Lord I lift Your name on high</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2></font2>
  <timestamp>9/4/2022  8:48</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd>null</bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[Lord I lift Your name on high, Lord I love to sing Your praises<BR>I'm so glad You're in my life, I'm so glad You came to save us<slide>You came from heaven to earth To show the way<BR>From the earth to the cross My debts to pay<BR><slide>From the cross to the grave From the grave to the sky<BR>Lord I lift Your name on high<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[null]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[undefined]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>Lord I offer my life to You</name>
  <font>Times New Roman</font>
  <font2></font2>
  <timestamp>5/19/2022  16:17</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd>null</bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[Lord, I offer my life to You Everything I've been through, use it for Your glory Lord I offer my days to You Lifting my praise to You as a pleasing sacrifice Lord I offer You my life<BR><slide>Things in the past, things yet unseen Wishes and dreams that are yet to come true All of my hopes, all of my plans My heart and my hands are lifted to You<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[null]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[undefined]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>Lord, I offer my life to You</name>
  <font>Times New Roman</font>
  <font2></font2>
  <timestamp>4/23/2022  8:16</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd>null</bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[Lord, I offer my life to You Everything I've been through, use it for Your glory Lord I offer my days to You Lifting my praise to You as a pleasing sacrifice Lord I offer You my life<BR><slide>Things in the past, things yet unseen Wishes and dreams that are yet to come true All of my hopes, all of my plans My heart and my hands are lifted to You<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[null]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[undefined]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>Lord, the light of your love is shining</name>
  <font>Times New Roman</font>
  <font2></font2>
  <timestamp>7/30/2022  17:25</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd>null</bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[Lord, the light of your love is shining In the midst of the darkness, shining Jesus, Light of the world, shine upon us Set us free by the truth you now bring us Shine on me, shine on me<slide>Shine, Jesus, shine Fill this land with the Father's glory Blaze, Spirit, blaze Set our hearts on fire Flow, river, flow Flood the nations with grace and mercy Send forth your word Lord, and let there be light<slide>Lord, I come to your awesome presence<BR>From the shadows into your radiance<BR>By the blood I may enter your brightness<BR>Search me, try me, consume all my darkness<BR>Shine on me, shine on me<slide>As we gaze on your kingly brightness So our faces display your likeness Ever changing from glory to glory Mirrored here may our lives tell your story Shine on me, shine on me<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide><slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[null]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[undefined]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>Make a joyful shout to the Lord Serve the lord</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2></font2>
  <timestamp>8/13/2022  11:50</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd>null</bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[Make a joyful shout to the Lord Serve the lord with gladness Come before His presence with singing Know that the Lord is God<BR><slide>Its He who's made us And we are His people<BR>The Sheep of His pasture And we are His People<slide>Enter into His gates With thanksgiving and with praise Be thankful to Him and bless His holy name<slide>For the Lord God is good His mercy is everlasting His faithfulness endures To all the generations<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide><slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[null]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[undefined]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>More About Jesus</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2>null</font2>
  <timestamp>null</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd></bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[More, more about Jesus;<BR>More, more about Jesus;<BR>More of His saving fullness see,<BR>More of His love who died for me. <slide>More about Jesus would I know,<BR>More of His grace to others show;<BR>More of His saving fullness see,<BR>More of His love who died for me. <slide>More about Jesus let me learn,<BR>More of His holy will discern;<BR>Spirit of God, my teacher be,<BR>Showing the things of Christ to me. <slide>More about Jesus in His word,<BR>Holding communion with my Lord,<BR>Hearing His voice in every line,<BR>Making each faithful saying mine. <slide>More about Jesus on His throne,<BR>Riches in glory all His own;<BR>More of His kingdom's sure increase;<BR>More of His coming, Prince of Peace.<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[null]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[null]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[null]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>My Jesus My Saviour Lord There Is None Like</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2></font2>
  <timestamp>4/23/2022  7:57</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd>null</bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[My Jesus My Saviour Lord There Is None Like You All Of My Life I Want To Praise The Wonders Of Your Mighty Love<slide>My Comfort My Shelter Tower Of Refuge And Strength Let Every Breath All That I Am Never Cease To Worship You.<slide>Shout To The Lord All The Earth Let Us Sing Power And Majesty Praise To The King Mountains Bow Down And The Seas Will Roar<BR>At The Sound Of Your Name<slide>I Sing For Joy At The Work Of Your Hands Forever I’ll Love You Forever I’ll Stand<BR>Nothing Compares To The Promise I Have In You.<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide><slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[null]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[undefined]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>Nearer My God To Thee</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2>null</font2>
  <timestamp>null</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd></bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[Nearer, my God, to Thee;<BR>Nearer, my God, to Thee,<BR>Nearer to Thee! <slide>Nearer, my God, to Thee,<BR>Nearer to Thee,<BR>E'en though it be a cross<BR>That raiseth me!<BR>Still all my song shall be, <slide>Though like the wanderer,<BR>The sun gone down,<BR>Darkness be over me,<BR>My rest a stone;<BR>Yet in my dreams I'd be, <slide>There let the way appear,<BR>Steps unto heaven;<BR>All that Thou sendest me,<BR>In mercy given;<BR>Angels to beckon me, <slide>Then, with my waking thoughts<BR>Bright with Thy praise,<BR>Out of my stony griefs<BR>Bethel I'll raise,<BR>So by my woes to be, <slide>Or if, on joyful wing<BR>Cleaving the sky,<BR>Sun, moon, and stars forgot,<BR>Upward I fly,<BR>Still all my song shall be,<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[null]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[null]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[null]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>O Come All Ye Faithful</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2></font2>
  <timestamp>5/27/2020  15:5</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd>null</bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[O come all ye faithful,<BR>Joyful and triumphant,<slide>O come ye, O come ye to Bethlehem;<BR>Come and behold Him,<slide>Born the King of angels:  <BR><slide>O come, let us adore Him,<BR>O come, let us adore Him,<slide>O come, let us adore Him,<BR>Christ the Lord. <slide>God of God,<BR>Light of light,<slide>Lo! He abhors not the virgin's womb;<BR>Very God,<slide>Begotton not created: <BR><slide>Sing, choirs of angels,<BR>Sing in exultation,<slide>Sing all ye citizens of heaven above:<BR>Glory to God<slide>In the highest: <BR><slide>Yea, Lord, we greet Thee,<BR>Born this happy morning,<slide>Jesus, to Thee be glory given;<BR>Word of the Father,<slide>Now in flesh appearing:<BR><slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide><slide><slide><slide><slide><slide><slide><slide><slide><slide><slide><slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[null]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[null]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[null]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>O Happy Day</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2>null</font2>
  <timestamp>null</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd></bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[Happy day, happy day,<BR>When Jesus washed my sins away!<BR>He taught me how to watch and pray,<BR>And live rejoicing every day. <slide>O happy day that fixed my choice<BR>On Thee, my Savior and my God!<BR>Well may this glowing heart rejoice,<BR>And tell its raptures all abroad. <slide>Tis done, the great transaction's done;<BR>I am my Lord's and He is mine.<BR>He drew me and I followed on,<BR>Charmed to confess the voice divine. <slide>Now rest, my long divided heart;<BR>Fixed on this blissful center; rest;<BR>Nor ever from my Lord depart,<BR>With Him of every good possessed. <slide>O happy bond that seals my vows<BR>To Him who merits all my love!<BR>Let cheerful anthems fill His house,<BR>While to that sacred shrine I move. <slide>High heaven, that heard the solemn vow,<BR>That vow renewed shall daily hear,<BR>Till in life's latest hour I bow<BR>And bless in death a bond so dear.<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[null]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[null]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[null]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>O Holy Night</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2>null</font2>
  <timestamp>null</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd></bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[Fall on your knees!<BR>Oh hear the angel voices!<BR>Oh night divine!<BR>Oh night when Christ was born,<BR>Oh night divine!<BR>Oh night, oh night divine! <slide>O holy night!<BR>The stars are brightly shining;<BR>It is the night<BR>Of the dear Savior's birth.<BR>Long lay the world<BR>In sin and error pining;<BR>Till He appeared<BR>And the soul felt its worth.<BR>A thrill of hope,<BR>The weary world rejoices;<BR>For yonder breaks,<BR>A new and glorious morn.<BR>Fall on your knees, <slide>Led by the light<BR>Of faith serenely beaming,<BR>With glowing hearts<BR>By His cradle we stand.<BR>So led by light<BR>Of a star sweetly gleaming,<BR>Here came the wise men<BR>From orient land.<BR>The King of kings<BR>Lay thus in lowly manger,<BR>In all our trials<BR>Born to be our Friend;<BR>He knows our need<BR>To our weakness is no stranger.<BR>Behold your King<BR>Before Him lowly bend;<BR>Behold your King<BR>Before Him lowly bend! <slide>Truly He taught us<BR>To love one another,<BR>His law is love<BR>And His gospel is peace;<BR>Chains shall He break<BR>For the slave is our brother,<BR>And in His name<BR>All oppression shall cease.<BR>Sweet hymns of joy<BR>In grateful chorus raise we,<BR>Let all within us<BR>Praise His holy name.<BR>Christ is the Lord<BR>O praise His name forever.<BR>His power and glory evermore proclaim;<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[null]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[null]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[null]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>Praise is rising eyes are turning to You</name>
  <font>Noto Sans Kannada SemiBold</font>
  <font2></font2>
  <timestamp>5/10/2025  21:48</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd></bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[Praise is rising, eyes are turning to You, we turn to You<BR>Hope is stirring, hearts are yearning for You, we long for You.<BR><slide>Cause when we see You, we find strength to face the day In Your Presence all our fears are washed away, washed away<slide>Hosanna, hosanna You are the God Who saves us, worthy of all our praises. Hosanna, hosanna Come have Your way among us We welcome You here, Lord Jesus<slide>Hear the sound of hearts returning to You, we turn to You In Your Kingdom broken lives are made new, You make us new<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide><slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>Shepherd of my soul I give You full control</name>
  <font></font>
  <font2></font2>
  <timestamp>11/3/2024  10:14</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd></bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[Shepherd of my soul I give You full control<BR>Wherever You may lead I will follow<BR><slide>I have made the choice to listen for Your voice<BR>Wherever You may lead I will go<slide>Be it in a quiet pasture or by a gentle breeze<BR>The shepherd of my soul is by my side<BR><slide>Should I face a mighty mountain or a valley dark and deep<BR>The shepherd of my soul will be my guide<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide><slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>Spirit of the sovereign Lord Come and make Your presence known Reveal</name>
  <font>Arial</font>
  <font2>Arial</font2>
  <timestamp>1/14/2023  17:43</timestamp>
  <yvideo>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cLfwXzN4pdI</yvideo>
  <bkgnd>null</bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[Spirit of the sovereign Lord Come and make Your presence known Reveal the glory of the Living God.<slide>Let the weight of Your glory cover us<BR>Let the life of Your river flow<slide>Let the truth of Your kingdom reign in us<BR>Let the weight of Your glory<BR>Let the weight of Your glory fall<slide>We do not seek Your hand<BR>We only seek Your face<slide>We want to know You We want to see You<BR>Reveal Your glory in this place<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide><slide><slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[SUNDAYSCHOOL]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[undefined]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>The Old Rugged Cross</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2>null</font2>
  <timestamp>null</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd></bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[So I'll cherish the old rugged cross,<BR>Till my trophies at last I lay down;<BR>I will cling to the old rugged cross,<BR>And exchange it some day for a crown. <slide>On a hill far away<BR>Stood an old rugged cross;<BR>The emblem of suffering and shame.<BR>And I love that old cross<BR>Where the dearest and best,<BR>For a world of lost sinners was slain. <slide>Oh, that old rugged cross,<BR>So despised by the world,<BR>Has a wondrous attraction for me;<BR>For the dear Lamb of God,<BR>Left His glory above,<BR>To bear it to dark Calvary. <slide>In the old rugged cross,<BR>Stained with blood so divine,<BR>A wondrous beauty I see;<BR>For 'twas on that old cross,<BR>Jesus suffered and died,<BR>To pardon and sanctify me. <slide>To the old rugged cross<BR>I will ever be true,<BR>It's shame and reproach gladly bear;<BR>Then He'll call me some day<BR>To my home far away,<BR>Where His glory forever I'll share.<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[null]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[null]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[null]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>These are the days of Elijah</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2></font2>
  <timestamp>4/23/2022  7:50</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd>null</bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[These are the days of Elijah Declaring the word of the Lord, yeah And these are the days of Your servant, Moses Righteousness being restored<slide>These are the days of great trials Of famine and darkness and sword Still we are the voice in the desert crying Prepare ye the way of the Lord!<BR><slide>behold He comes, riding on the clouds Shining like the sun, at the trumpet's call Lift your voice, (it's) the year of Jubilee Out of Zion's hill, salvation comes<slide>And these are the days of Ezekiel The dry bones becoming as flesh And these are the days of Your servant, David Rebuilding the temple of praise<slide>And these are the days of the harvest The fields are all white in the world And we are the laborers that are in Your vineyard Declaring the Word of the Lord<slide>There's no God like Jehovah! There's no God like Jehovah! There's no God like Jehovah! There's no God like Jehovah!<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide><slide><slide><slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[null]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[undefined]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>This is my desire you to honor you</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2></font2>
  <timestamp>4/23/2022  8:32</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd>null</bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[This is my desire you to honor you Lord, with all my heart I worship you All I have within me I give You praise All that I adore is in you<slide>Lord I give you my heart I give you my soul<BR>I live for you alone Every breath that I take<BR>Every moment I'm awake Lord have Your way in me<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[null]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[undefined]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>Water You turned into wine</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2></font2>
  <timestamp>4/23/2022  8:21</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd>null</bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[Water You turned into wine, opened the eyes of the blind there's no one like You, none like You! Into the darkness You shine, out of the ashes we rise there's no one like You, none like You!<slide>Our God is greater, our God is stronger God, You are higher than any other Our God is Healer, awesome in power Our God! Our God!<slide>And if our God is for us, then who could ever stop us? And if our God is with us, then what could stand against?<BR><slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[null]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[undefined]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>We Bring The Sacrifice Of Praise</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2>null</font2>
  <timestamp>null</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd></bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[We bring the sacrifice of praise<BR>Into the house of the Lord<BR>We bring the sacrifice of praise<BR>Into the house of the Lord<BR>And we offer up to You<BR>The sacrifices of thanksgiving<BR>And we offer up to You<BR>The sacrifices of joy<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[null]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[null]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[null]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>Welcome Holy Spirit We are in Your presence</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2></font2>
  <timestamp>4/23/2022  8:38</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd>null</bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[Welcome Holy Spirit We are in Your presence<BR>Fill us with Your power Live inside of me<slide>You’re the Living Water Never drying Fountain<BR>Comforter and Counselor Take complete control<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[null]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[undefined]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>What A Friend We Have In Jesus</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2>null</font2>
  <timestamp>null</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd></bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[What a Friend we have in Jesus,<BR>All our sins and griefs to bear!<BR>What a privilege to carry,<BR>Everything to God in prayer!<BR>Oh, what peace we often forfeit,<BR>Oh, what needless pain we bear.<BR>All because we do not carry<BR>Everything to God in prayer! <slide>Have we trials and temptations?<BR>Is there trouble anywhere?<BR>We should never be discouraged;<BR>Take it to the Lord in prayer.<BR>Can we find a friend so faithful,<BR>Who will all our sorrows share?<BR>Jesus knows our every weakness;<BR>Take it to the Lord in prayer. <slide>Are we weak and heavy laden,<BR>Cumbered with a load of care?<BR>Precious Savior, still our refuge!<BR>Take it to the Lord in prayer.<BR>Do Thy friends despise forsake Thee?<BR>Take it to the Lord in prayer.<BR>In His arms He'll take and shield Thee;<BR>Thou wilt find a solace there.<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[null]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[null]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[null]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>When upon life</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2></font2>
  <timestamp>3/11/2023  19:4</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd>null</bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[Count your blessings Name them one by one.<BR>Count your blessings See what God hath done.<BR>Count your blessings Name them one by one.<BR>Count your many blessings See what God hath done. <slide>When upon life's billows You are tempest tossed, When you are discouraged Thinking all is lost, Count your many blessings Name them one by one, And it will surprise you What the Lord hath done. <slide>Are you ever burdened With a load of care,<BR>Does the cross seem heavy You are called to bear. Count your many blessings Every doubt will fly, And you will be singing As the days go by. <slide>When you look at others With their lands and gold, Think that Christ has promised You His wealth untold. Count your many blessings Money cannot buy, Your reward in heaven Nor your home on high. <slide>So amid the conflict Whether great or small,<BR>Do not be discouraged God is over all. Count your many blessings Angels will attend, Help and comfort give you To your journey's end.<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide><slide><slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[null]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[undefined]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>You Are My Refuge You Are My Fortress</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2>Alegreya Sans</font2>
  <timestamp>8/24/2024  20:29</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd></bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[You are my Refuge you are my fortress<BR>You are my Friend in need you are my Lord<slide>And I will worship You with all my heart <BR>And I Will Seek Your Face all through my life <BR>I will serve you Lord with all that I have Here I am<BR>Here I am O Lord! Here I am<slide>You are my Savior, You are my Healer<BR>You are my Strength in need, You are my God<slide>You are my Shepherd, You are my Conqueror<BR>You are my Hiding place, You are my God<slide>HERE I AM OH LORD HERE I AM OH LORD<BR>HERE I AM OH LORD HERE I AM<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide><slide><slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>You Are My Strength When I Am Weak</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2></font2>
  <timestamp>5/27/2023  16:28</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd>null</bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[You Are My Strength When I Am Weak You Are The Treasure That I Seek, You Are My All In All<slide>Seeking You As A Precious Jewel Lord, To Give Up I Would Be A Fool, You Are My All In All<slide>Jesus, Lamb Of God Worthy Is Your Name<BR>Jesus, Lamb Of God Worthy Is Your Name<slide>Taking My Sin, My Cross, My Shame Rising Again I Bless Your Name, You Are My All In All<slide>When I Fall Down You Pick Me Up When I Am Dry You Fill My Cup, You Are My All In All.<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide><slide><slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[undefined]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>You are here moving in our midst</name>
  <font>Calibri</font>
  <font2></font2>
  <timestamp>4/30/2022  10:28</timestamp>
  <yvideo></yvideo>
  <bkgnd>null</bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[You are here, moving in our midst I worship You I worship You You are here, working in this place I worship You I worship You<BR><slide>You are Way maker, miracle worker, promise keeper Light in the darkness My God, that is who You are You are<BR><slide>You are here, touching every heart I worship You I worship You You are here, healing every heart I worship You I worship You<BR><slide>You are here turning lives around I worship You I worship You You are here You mended every heart I worship You I worship You<BR><slide>Even when I don't see it, you’re working Even when I don't feel it, You're working<BR>You never stop, You never stop working You never stop, You never stop working<BR><slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide><slide><slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[null]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[undefined]]></subcat>
</song>
<song>
  <category>English1</category>
  <name>You deserve the glory And the honour</name>
  <font>Alegreya Sans</font>
  <font2>Alegreya Sans</font2>
  <timestamp>5/4/2024  18:27</timestamp>
  <yvideo>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lscDXdfiBdw</yvideo>
  <bkgnd></bkgnd>
  <key></key>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <notes></notes>
  <slide><![CDATA[You deserve the glory And the honour<BR>Lord we lift our hands in worship As we lift your holy name<slide>For you are great, You do miracles so great. There is no one else like you, there is no one else like You<slide>]]></slide>
  <slide2><![CDATA[<slide><slide>]]></slide2>
  <name2><![CDATA[]]></name2>
  <tags><![CDATA[]]></tags>
  <slideseq><![CDATA[]]></slideseq>
  <subcat><![CDATA[]]></subcat>
</song>
</songDB>
